export const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    questionText:
      "A 24-Year-Old Student Returns From A Gap Year In Malawi Complaining Of Visible Haematuria, Dysuria And Urinary Frequency. She Says She Felt Well Throughout Her Trip But Experienced An Itchy Rash On Her Legs A Few Hours After Swimming In Lake Malawi Which Has Now Resolved.",
    rightAnswers: [1, 2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
    table: true,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    questionText:
      "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    rightAnswers: [3],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    questionText:
      "A 24-Year-Old Student Returns From A Gap Year In Malawi Complaining Of Visible Haematuria, Dysuria And Urinary Frequency. She Says She Felt Well Throughout Her Trip But Experienced An Itchy Rash On Her Legs A Few Hours After Swimming In Lake Malawi Which Has Now Resolved.",
    rightAnswers: [4, 2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    questionText:
      "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    rightAnswers: [2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    questionText:
      "A 24-Year-Old Student Returns From A Gap Year In Malawi Complaining Of Visible Haematuria, Dysuria And Urinary Frequency. She Says She Felt Well Throughout Her Trip But Experienced An Itchy Rash On Her Legs A Few Hours After Swimming In Lake Malawi Which Has Now Resolved.",
    rightAnswers: [4, 2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    questionText:
      "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    rightAnswers: [2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    questionText:
      "A 24-Year-Old Student Returns From A Gap Year In Malawi Complaining Of Visible Haematuria, Dysuria And Urinary Frequency. She Says She Felt Well Throughout Her Trip But Experienced An Itchy Rash On Her Legs A Few Hours After Swimming In Lake Malawi Which Has Now Resolved.",
    rightAnswers: [5, 2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    questionText:
      "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    rightAnswers: [3, 5],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    questionText:
      "A 24-Year-Old Student Returns From A Gap Year In Malawi Complaining Of Visible Haematuria, Dysuria And Urinary Frequency. She Says She Felt Well Throughout Her Trip But Experienced An Itchy Rash On Her Legs A Few Hours After Swimming In Lake Malawi Which Has Now Resolved.",
    rightAnswers: [1, 2],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    questionText:
      "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    rightAnswers: [3, 4, 5],
    options: [
      {
        id: 1,
        text: "Answer 1",
        perc: 7,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        text: "Answer 2",
        perc: 5,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        text: "Answer 3",
        perc: 30,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        text: "Answer 4",
        perc: 40,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        text: "Answer 5",
        perc: 80,
      },
    ],
  },
] as any[];
